[Music]
you're listening to the AI native Dev
brought to you by
[Music]
Tesla hello everyone welcome back to the
AI native Dev today we have a really
exciting guest who I've known for the
past five six years now and I've had
amazing conversation with and that's
Tamar yushua Tamar thanks for coming on
to the show thanks so much for having me
Tamar is is amazing in various ways and
had illustrious career right maybe put
some highlights from that from that sort
of engineering and product leadership
career which include being a VP at
Amazon or A9 being a VP at Google
notably own search as part of the
journey which is relevant to what you're
doing today were a chief product officer
at slack where we met because you also
became a board member at at sneak at the
time and now you are the president of
products and Technology at gleen is that
right am I missing anything important in
the in the journey that that's awesome
and the most important part was being on
the board at sneak where I got to meet
you yeah this was a definitely a fun fun
highlight times on it and and got
conversations that span well past the
the sneak context today as we get going
we'll talk about AI in the Enterprise
we'll talk about building products with
a eye context we'll talk about you know
figuring out how to how to Wrangle them
in the first place maybe start us off by
just explaining a little bit what does
gleen do so gleen is an Enterprise AI
platform what we do is we read the
content of all of your SAS applications
we ingest information for Microsoft
Office 365 from Google from slack from
Salesforce from jira and make it easy to
find information across all of your SAS
tools and also to ask questions in
natural language so you can think of it
as chat GPT for your Enterprise and chat
GPT you ask questions about the world
and in glean you can ask questions about
your Enterprise proprietary information
within your Enterprise and we also have
a platform that you can access all this
information we call it the knowledge
graph of your Enterprise through our
apis and EI and have a platform also for
building no code application so anything
that you want to do that's building AI
on top of all of the information that's
stored in all of these different SAS
apps you can do through G yeah so super
interesting and and the bread the is is
also interesting so you're first of all
just clarification is it more about
discovering a piece of information
that's scattered somewhere across the
the the Enterprise systems and and
linking to them more kind of search
orientation or is it more around you
actually processing and understanding
those things and bringing back some
summarized answer for it so both so you
can use it for both so let's say I'm
going on a customer call and I want to
know who's the account executive for it
I can ask lean really simply who's the
AE for this account or who's the CSN I
can also ask what were the latest
outages I can say bring um write me a
brief a customer brief for this for this
meeting and then it'll go through
everything it'll go through what were
the latest meetings what's the status of
the accountant sales force what's the
what were the outages that I should know
and it'll put that together I have to
write the prompt that will put it
together in the way that I want to
consume it and it will summarize that
and give me the information I do this
often like any Prospect tell me about
the prospect what stage is it in what
should I know and now I don't have to
have a CSM write a briefing for me I can
do it myself so that's an example so it
does both of any kind of capabilities
that chat GPT would have we can do
through glean and we keep on adding
functionality as well to be able to do
better at summarization and insights got
so it sounds like it is primarily the
chat GPT like you've used that analogy
so it's more the chat GPT than the
Google for your yeah so we have both
interfaces so we have an interface that
looks like Google search but over your
your Enterprise so we have two different
the search Inter it's in the chat
interface and then we have what we
called ai ai answers so think of Google
introduced AI overviews recently where
you can get an AI overview and slack we
have the equivalent of AI answers in the
search interface so that kind of brings
them together as well and then we also
have the equivalent of custom gpts that
you can do on chat GPT for a specific
use case those are called glean apps got
it and they extend and personalize the I
guess kind of the system prompts or the
ability to to represent some subset of
the Enterprise data and in some formal
of interaction like T exactly so a good
example of the glean app is most of our
customers want to build an HR app to say
these are the canonical documents for HR
so that let's say somebody wrote an
answer in a slack channel to a question
that was wrong it wouldn't pick that up
but here are all the HR apps so here's
your knowledge base you should be
looking at here's when it should trigger
here's the kind of prompts that it
should use and it's specialized for that
and glean will actually autor route so
if you ask a question in glean and say
what's our vacation policy it will autor
route to the glean app the HR app and
then you can also the HR team who build
the glean app can build actions to
actually file your vacation through that
glean app and what's nice about it is
that it is no code so an HR person who
does not know how to code can build a
glean app interesting so I guess we'll
come back to the to the building piece
because I think that's really
interesting the search uh angle of it
just to say I guess the maybe this is
still the sneak DNA piece of it but like
immediately I get a little bit worried
on the security front of that it
implies A system that is very
knowledgeable and you're telling me
stuff about a client but how do you know
if I'm allowed to do that and I think
that's a it's a thorny domain at the
moment in the in the in the world of AI
I guess how do you how do you think or
handle compartmentalizing who should
have access to what data so that was
probably the most important thing that
glean did in the early days is took
security privacy policies really
seriously so it didn't start by search
and then we'll figure out the Privacy
later it started privacy first from the
get-go so we have over 100 connectors to
all your different apps and we
understand the privacy and governance of
each app and we understand the metadata
that tells us like for slack we know
which channels are private public what
are private DMS for Google Docs think of
it you've got a Google doc and let's say
you share it with me with the
permissions anyone with the link can see
it but now my neighbor over here you
didn't share it with them so they are
not supposed to see it Leen needs to
know that I can see it but they can't
and so how do we know that we know
because we can see your email and your
teams conversations and your slack
conversations we can know if it was
shared with you if we don't see that it
was shared with you we don't let you
have access to that so we really
understand the different policies for
each of the SAS apps and we make sure
that we abide by them and it's very
rigorous in what we do but now as you
like with your ceso mind will say wait a
minute maybe I don't want everyone in
the organization to have access to all
information that is not locked down
because there might be some people who
created a document and didn't do the
permissions right it's security through
obscurity well you never would have
found that document but now with glean
you can find this so I can say when's
the next riff and if there happens to be
a document about a riff that somebody in
HR didn't get the permissions right I
would find it so another thing that
we've done is we have ai governance
modules that we will enable a company
before they launch to assess if they
have documents that shouldn't be open
and we will flag certain types of
documents at for people to review and we
will enable a company to Red list or
green list like you can red list hold
directories or hold types of documents
to say no matter what the permissions
are we never want these to show up and
glean yeah so how's the let me D be
doubtful a little bit here for a second
so like in llm world when you feed the
llm knowledge if the llm understands or
or is aware of you know a riff generally
the perception in the security world is
you can convince it to tell you uh there
isn't like the ability to it's one thing
to define the policy which is a
challenge in its own right which I guess
it's easier for me to grock how you
would do that and also maybe a human
will verify that and and confirm it but
in the moment request s how who enforces
these policies and and is it llm is it
the same gen systems that know this or
there no secret SAU here how is this how
is this compartmentalized in a more
assured way so I have to explain the
architecture more so we do not fine-tune
models with your Enterprise data because
you're absolutely right if you fine-tune
a model with your Enterprise data or you
do a large context window with all the
information the llm is just going to
know that information and that's why why
it's so hard to do this in the
Enterprise so it is a rag based solution
and all of the enforcements are based on
the the search the retrieval part of rag
so we only so the way that the
architecture works in the for the
assistant in the natural language query
you put in a query in natural language
we call the llm for the planning phase
where we take that query and we
translate it into search queries then we
create our retrieval engine and we get
back the relevant snippet so this is
just search it's finding what are the
right documents based on your
permissions and then that is the context
window that's fed into the ACT phase and
now we call the llms in order to
generate an answer so that information
if you didn't have the the right
security for to see the information will
never get fed into the llm and so that's
how we secure it and ensure it yeah and
I think that makes sense and I think
aligns with the best practice ice that
that I'm aware of in the world of
security which is you want to pull in
the data from a bit more bread and
butter systems or I know traditional
systems if you will with authorization
systems in which it says Tomar is
allowed to do see this and guy is
allowed to see that um and then yeah you
can massage and and present and process
that data uh in the right fashion for it
and the other thing that people are are
very worried about the security and
organizations is it really is sensitive
because we're we are indexing all of
your organization data is we actually
allow people to host it in their own
environment so in their own gcp project
or AWS project so it doesn't leave their
Cloud
premises so what type of limitations do
you need to take on because you don't
train on the customer data what could
you do and and this is I'm I'm thinking
about this a little bit with the with
the mindset of code and I'm thinking
indexing on your code base is a topic
we've already discussed a few times in
the podcast and there's elements also s
of pros and cons to it there's a certain
amount of if you brought in Bad Code you
might replicate mistakes and things like
that but generally there it's a scary
proposition for a lot of organizations
because they will be giving one of these
Giants access to their code and they're
afraid legitimately or otherwise that
their data will be there um but if you
don't do
that there's a lot less or at least my
understanding is there's a lot less you
could do in terms of feeding that
Insight of your code into the code
generation is that true over here what
what is sacrifice I think the use cases
are not as important in this case so you
could say I want to make sure that all
of the tone of any documentation or any
marketing collateral anything that comes
out of glean is consistent across
everything that everyone is doing so you
can still have as input guidelines and
that can be part of your input and so
you can create a glean app that says
here our guidelines of how we want it to
be but then you're the user is going to
have to more explicitly do that and say
follow these guidelines as opposed to
glean understanding without the user
telling them here's what I would like to
do but what I find is in those kind of
cases like marketing will say these are
the marketing guidelines or engineering
will say here's the template for the
design doc and product will say here's
we follow the template for prds so it
isn't as much of a problem in practice
because you don't ingest all the code
and find the style of this organization
so it's not as it hasn't come up as an
issue yeah it's interesting it's a it
feels a little bit like you're not
trying to regenerate things in the style
of the data that you encounter you're
trying to find it and interpret it but
you're not trying to create a new
customer record based on this
conversation because of this and
therefore you want to have processed and
digested all the previous custom records
to to doing it you're trying to to
understand if you want to get a custom
record in a standard fashion then
someone can build a glean app that
defines what is that fashion how do you
want to see that and then you can find
the right data to populate into it
exactly and that's going to become
really interesting with the glean apps
of where are the ways that we can
automate so once you get actions then
you get much more automation much more
productivity savings because you can
adjust all these things so for example
you can ingest all of your gong calls so
one thing that we built the PM team at
clean built an app to look through gong
calls tease out the information in the
call put it in a spreadsheet and then be
able to assess what are the most
frequently Asked requests from customers
so this is like
multi-step super interesting examples
but you don't need it all fed into an
llm but I need to it's more specific use
cases and that's where things get like
really interesting yeah no I can see the
power in it and so still a little bit on
sort of the gleen journey and we'll
we'll talk about the sausage making and
I guess we got a little bit into the
sausage making here in architecture Gan
predates I think gen right I think it
was founded and it was an AI company at
the time as well can you tell us a
little bit about what was before like
what you're describing right now sounds
a very genish company tell us a little
bit about what was there before was this
a pivot was this a an natural expansion
how did that go about yeah so gleen
started in 2019 it was founded by Arvin
Jane Arvin was an early Google search
infrastructure engineer so he was one of
the people who built the original search
infrastructure for Google search I
actually worked with him and Google back
in the day in like 2011 so we know each
other from there and and then we he went
on to rubric where he was the found one
of the co-founders of rubric and then at
rubric as they were growing he found
that tivity decreased instead of
increased and a lot of it was around
finding information and by the way we
see that with our customers too they
come to us and they're like ah we've
grown we can't find the information we
need to get our job done so he's like
why is there not a good Enterprise
search solution so that's how it started
is building Enterprise search but
because he came from Google he knew that
AI was being used in search at the time
like Bert the original models the
precursor llms were built by Google why
to improve search so they had been used
since I think 2016 17 in search The Bert
models Vector embeddings were used to
improve the quality of search so from
the beginning glean was an AI search
company it was using Bert for its models
it was building Vector embeddings before
people were talking about Vector
databases they fine-tune their own
models per Enterprise to build the
vector embeddings so this is why gle's
Enterprise search was so much better
than anything else on the market but
this is this was search it was Google
search for your organization data it was
around AI the same way Google uses AI
which is I can connect the dots between
whatever WS that are actually similar I
can understand May a bit bit context so
like all of these Vector databases the
embeddings uh type solution semantic
matching so got it and I guess to an
extent he built what would have been the
Google appliance that at some point came
in went for the Enterprise that that
connects all these dots but it wasn't
generating answers it was pointing
source of information it was using Mi uh
AI as an ml so it was using what was AI
at the time but it wasn't using
generative AI so it was just Enterprise
search you put in a query you find the
documents but it was a better Enterprise
search than anything else out there it
the answers were just more relevant then
started selling as price search and then
how was the transition was it a sort of
like run the alarm Ring the Alarm all
hands- on Deck were switching to this
sort of gen thing was it a more gradual
let's try this out it was gpt3 came out
and because we already had an AI team at
people were keeping up with things it
wasn't like a surprise right and gpt3
came out and said we should have a
natural language assistant interface
into clean and and there was a war room
get everyone together and build the
assistant and then it was build the with
the architecture that I described it was
put the generative aspect into the
product and then they started they
already always sold Enterprise search
and then they added on the assistant and
as you could buy either search or the
assistant now we're one product together
but this was it was a very fast pivot to
Let's had this assistant because now
chat GPT came out and every CIO was
saying we need an AI solution so then
they can turn to glean and glean has an
assistant it's an AI solution right so
it was exactly I wouldn't say it was a
pivot because all of the technology that
was built for search was the r in rag
it's the retrieval in rag was they had a
clean had a head start on everyone else
because for four years had been building
conectors had taken understood privacy
and security and had built the retrieval
engine because the exact same retrieval
engine is what that was built for
Enterprise search is being used for the
assistant yeah but it's it feels like a
totally different user experience though
and almost a different positioning right
what you've described right now wasn't
hey we started with your That's History
now that's a piece of the puzzle and the
the interface the front door the way you
engage with a product with as a gen
product is that assistant is the
composition not just finding the data
but most of the time it's less about
sending me to the authoritative source
and more about digesting what you found
for me so we were going through this
transition as everyone was starting to
get used to chat gbt and doing some
searches on Google some searches on chat
gbt or perplexity or V Gemini and to
it's the same thing you can toggle
between the interfaces and glean you can
go to the search interface you can go to
the assistant interface so yeah it was
another product built on top of the
Foundation because the foundation how we
deploy how we secure all of that stayed
the same so it was the user interface on
top and of course marketing had to
change and the messaging had to change
and all that and there's a new team
that's building the assistant so yeah it
was an expansion absolute expansion and
then more recently about six months ago
we added the platform on it as well so
each of these are gradual expansions to
the amount of functionality and
capabilities understood and I think this
probably a good time to raise this so I
have this hypothesis that I asked Dez
from intercom as well in the previous
episode which is that when you think
about AI I oftentimes think about tools
across these sort of two axes I think
about a trust axis and a change axis so
on one hand is how much does it ask me
to change how I work and on the other
hand how much do I need to trust it to
get it right so the more autonomous it
is the more I need to trust it to get it
right I'm going to put it say for
example in fin the intercom support
agent I need to put it in front of
customers I need to trust that it it
gets it right I can spot check things
but I can't have a human verify the
results that defeats the whole purpose
and I guess my my my thesis is that if
your product is already text based so
it's already a search it's already a
chat it's already I guess chat has like
the slack version of chat has the
intercon version of chat then at least
the change Vector it's easier to
introduce AI because I guess those are
more naturally the way that you would
interface and it's easier to imagine a a
user on the other side does that sound
right to you I mean you've seen slack
you've been Google you're now at glean
on it is it easier or I guess in general
how hard is it for people to go from
accepting you're going to point me to a
link to to somewhere else versus you'll
summarize to me or even just the
interaction the fact that they are in
chat mode versus in search
mode I believe that behavior changes
hard people just they're get used to
doing things in a certain way even look
at the retention numbers for chat PT
people try it they play with it and then
they forget that they can use it because
you're not used to using it it's not in
your daily routine change is hard and it
needs a lot of repetition and while I
agree that if you have a text interface
getting a chat interface on because
you're already talking in natural
language like with slack you're put
putting in messages and and they're with
Gan you're putting in queries but the
biggest stumbling block we have is
people understanding what they can and
can't do with it so it's not that okay
now I have a chat interface it's what
can I use this chat interface for search
if you think about it when Google search
first came out with queries people
didn't understand it either what's a
query like now everybody knows what a
query is how to formulate a query how to
reformulate a query you do a query you
don't get the results you refactor it
and you do it again this is just like
part of life and right people got used
to it but it wasn't that way in the
beginning you didn't know how to put a
query into get the right answer so we're
going through that phase with the
assistant now is that people come to the
assistant and some people understand AI
they understand like the whole flow and
like Engineers understand how it's built
so they have the mental model of what it
can and can't do but then you put it out
to people who have not interacted with
chatbots before with AI chat not I'm not
talking about customer support because
customer support is such a different use
case it's like very small set of
questions that people ask as opposed to
universe is open I can ask anything so
we have people coming to glean and being
like what should my priority be for next
week where there's no way glean could
know that information because it doesn't
have the information and people don't
yet realize these are the questions that
can be answered so while I agree with
you the transition is easier when you go
to the assistant what you can do what
will work and what won't work like the
example I gave you of the PMS creating
this way to analyze gone calls somebody
outside of the product pay atan about
that as a possibility yeah they wouldn't
even occur to them that they could do
this but as we get more used to this and
I contend as the Next Generation grows
up with chat GPT and grows up with these
products it'll be like the generation
that grew up with Google search it'll
become clearer and become more obvious
and the models will get better
and they'll get stronger yeah
interesting I find the the decision that
Google has made to introduce the AI
answers into the same interface putting
aside potential antitrust aspects to it
but from a ux perspective is a great way
to engage people on it because they put
in the search they get a thing they get
some answer and yeah they can just
scroll down and get what they are used
to getting but in the meantime they've
been exposed to that answer and they
build those out and I'm curious glean in
theory could do the same thing right you
could toggle as you mentioned between
the interfaces but you could also build
something that's the same that answers
at the top we we actually do have that
we have what we call AI answers we
actually had it before the AI overviews
of Google but we do exactly that we have
an AI answer and you can click more and
then it expands down and it'll get the
full answer and that is exactly that
we're careful on how often we trigger
because you want to make make sure that
it's going to have it's going to be the
right answer basically yeah because one
of the challenges is also is when you go
to search you voice a query in a certain
way and when you go to the assistant you
voice it in a different way right so
there's also the expectation of the user
and how they're communicating so you get
better quality assistant answers when
you understand you're going to the
assistant to chat but we absolutely do
that a lot of the engagement with the
assistant is through the search
interface and the AI answers that they
get in the search interface and we're
going to be doing more of that more of
automatically triggering one or the
other I feel like in the future there
won't be these two interfaces and the
other thing that we do is that when
you're in the assistant we give you we
tell you which query we used to query
the rag and we give you the documents
that were accessed so that you can go
back and you can click on those
documents to go and it's not only
there's the citations but there's also
here's the list of documents that we
used for the answer so in a way you're
merging both directions you're making it
easy to go from the assistant back to
search search to the assistant so in a
year I think these all will get merged
into one and you won't have one or the
other yeah it's interesting I find a lot
of compelling aspects to integration
like this because the user gets the
choice and and you get to interact with
it and I keep coming back a little bit
to that limitations question which is I
think a bit hard to tell and depends on
how well people build those policies and
I think it's also easier to
accept that in Enterprise in the
Enterprise even if the the breadth of
knowledge is bigger than just customer
support it is still vastly smaller than
the the whole web and that information
and so maybe it's okay to say that over
here the security and the element of
controlling who can see what takes
precedence and you lose some neural
connections that might have been made
that would have been non-trivial if you
had fed all this information into the
llm but that's okay that's a fair
trade-off to me
yes so I guess let's talk indeed keep
promising talking about the sausage
making let's do that now I guess what is
it like building a product that works
this way the the the results of the
product vary by the data that comes in
the success rates are very different and
that's on top of the fact that the llms
move at such a kind of lightening pace
and so you get new models all the time
and if I understand correctly you
actually even don't pick the model you
have to work with models that the
customer does so maybe tell us a little
bit about how do you interact with the
models just said that but what I'm
really interested is you talked about km
as a judge you had a post about this
just how do you know that your product
works it's very difficult so it's the
non-deterministic aspect is the most
interesting and challenging my first
week at glean I was talking to the head
of the assistant quality team just to
learn what do you do and how does it
work and realize that a lot of their
time was was spent talking to customers
who did not have the right expectations
of what the what it could do or were
complaining that it was
non-deterministic I did this query once
I did it again and it didn't get the
same thing and we're starting to get
used to chat GPT and this the concept of
non-deterministic but in an Enterprise
you're a CIO you buy software you pay a
lot of money for it you expect it to
have the same answer every time and so
one is getting our customers comfortable
with what llms can do and what the
boundary conditions are is part of what
we have to do in our product and it
can't just be in the marketing and in
the enablement you have to have some way
in the product to take care of this as
well to understand what are the
challenges going to be for people so I
explained the rag architecture so we
have our way of evaluating the search
which most of the team came from Google
search ranking built eval tools just
like Google search head so that kind of
that's like br
like how do you eval search we have a
whole process for Ev this is not the
user side this is internal this is toate
whether your search is working correctly
with information the the engineers see
your engineers this is our ranking the
ranking algorithms with a lot of
information on exactly what was
triggered and what wasn't and what
scores it had now it is a little bit
more difficult because at Google you
could use thirdparty Raiders to say
here's a change we're making is this
change good or bad evaluate it because
this is Enterprise data we can't use
third party Raiders we can only use our
tools and Engineers to look at the data
so that's a another wrinkle on top for
for Enterprise but but going back to
your question of what's different is
understanding the user mindset when
they're using this product how do you
help them through that to give them
guard rails so they can better
understand what the product can do and
then how do you evaluate it and how do
you make sure that it's working as
intended with this new technology that
nobody fully understands why it's giving
the answer that it does yeah what are
some examples of things that you would
do in the product to to help to help
people understand so a big one is
suggest one of the things about glean is
that we understand your organization so
in the uh connectors that we do we also
have a workday connector active
directory so we understand who you are
who's who are your peers who's on your
team so we can suggest prompts that
people in your team has been have been
using oh you're a PM here's a prompt
from another PM that things that they've
been doing that you might want to try
and so we can suggest or generic
suggestions we've been experimenting
with all different ones but that can
help guide people into areas of this is
the right this is ways that you can get
value and that's going to be really
important and we want to do a lot more
of that and the clean apps was a big way
of doing that as well here's some more
structured prompts and triggers this is
where if you want have an it question
you'll go here if you have a want to
build a customer brief here's a glean
app for building a customer brief so
that helps people go to things that
somebody has curated somebody like the
5% of people in the company who really
understand how to work with prompts and
llms they're going to do that and
they're going to help and we're going to
be doing more and more of that and I
hope that is a way that's a whole
another angle of how we are doing that
and then we also have just teams
dedicated to eval and understanding what
changes need to be made what don't how
to evaluate new models um as you
mentioned we customers can decide what
model they want to use we validate the
model we certify it I should say if
Gemini 1.5 Pro comes out so we will
certify it for our customers before we
enable them to use it but we have let
our customers pick open AI anthropic or
Gemini for the llm aspect of the work
and so so that's another thing that's
tricky also is working with the
different models but how so I I
understand in like the suggest notion or
the idea of disseminating actually
probably a useful practice for any
product not an llm specific one which is
take the forerunners and provide an easy
way to disseminate the their sample uses
to the rest of the organization but on
the other side in terms of what happens
if it fails what happens if
hallucinations are a thing in this world
so ranges from we didn't
okay maybe you're good on the search
side so it finds the relevant data you
feel pretty good but did it understand
it did it process it correctly did it
present it correctly how do you evaluate
it when you certify what types of tools
are at your disposal to know when you're
using a new model or even just evolving
your software that it got better in so
first of all in the product customers
can do a thumbs up thumbs down obviously
we get more thumbs down than thumbs up
because that's just the nature of people
but we but that helpful until all those
queries go come back to us so that we
know here's a set of of bad queries we
also evaluate things like can search
it's easy did somebody click on it did
they find what they were looking for in
the assistant it's trickier because they
might have gotten the answer or not
gotten the answer but for example if
they try a couple queries in assistant
and go to search afterwards and then
find the document that they needed we
know that the assistant didn't give them
the answer so we have some we have a
metric the index the satisfaction index
from search and the assistant so we look
at that and we measure that very heavily
of how many bad queries did we get how
many thumbs down did we get so that's
one yeah and that's close those are all
things that people using the product
right that's the proxy for how well are
we doing and if we're doing hill
climbing to improve is it going up or
going down and then evaluating is super
tricky so we have as you mentioned we've
started using llm as a judge and there
are many ways that that the llm could go
wrong or the whole assist assistant
could go wrong it could pick the wrong
query to send to the retrieval engine
the retrieval could not find the
document it could find the wrong one or
it could miss some something and then in
the generative not be a complete answer
it could not be grounded in the facts it
might pull in public data instead of the
data that you had and then so you've got
the completeness the groundedness and
the factualness so we've been using llms
to judge
are answers for the assistant in these
different areas so completeness is one
that we get the most thumbs down if it's
not a complete answer we'll get thumbs
down for it and then we've correlated
the thumbs down with llm as a judge and
the completeness so that's the most
easiest for an llm to then evaluate the
results of the llm yeah and so we have
completeness we have grounded did it
tell you which which context it came
from and then the factualness is the
hard
and the factualness what you need is a
golden set essentially being the you did
not hallucinate grounded is more of the
hallucinations okay we don't have a big
problem with hallucinations at glean
because of the rag based architecture
and because we do the citations so it
the groundedness is the most aligned to
to hallucinations but sometimes it's not
grounded in Enterprise stock because it
might be like the stock price that you
ask for for a company and it might just
be public knowledge the factfulness is
was it LMS are very confident so they'll
say with great confidence that something
is correct and then a user will not
thumbs down those because they'll just
assume it's correct those are the most
dangerous right and that what we're
doing is trying to actually have a
golden set we having an llm extract
queries from documents and then measure
the effectiveness of Are We finding them
so we get the golden set and then we're
so this one actually we're still working
on the fact
how to best measure it but the best part
that we've done now is now we have a
repeatable process for llm is Judge we
have an e evil framework of how we use
and we can just turn the crank when a
new model comes out and we can get an
evaluation across these metrics for new
models and for changes as we're making
changes in the code we can evaluate them
more easily is it perfect no but it's a
lot better than Engineers manually going
and looking at every query and that
golden set needs to be created per
customer so we use a lot of times we use
our data for some of these golden sets
to make sure but we do have in our eval
we actually run queries in our customer
environments in their deployments
because we can't look at their content
but we can run things and evaluate them
and get the results of the evaluation so
that's interesting and that's a good
learning so in you can't look at their
data you have to uh make sure that your
check did not cause problems with their
data or see at least try to assess
that's the case so what you're agreeing
with them is that you'd be able to run
some processes that are not actually
functional like run a bunch of these
tests on their platform with their data
but you won't access the data you just
get the results of like thumbs up thumbs
down different version of the thumbs up
thumbs down to say yeah feels good for
you to to deploy this this new version
or to opgrade to this new model Etc
we're very cautious of making sure we
have very strict agreements of how we're
handling customer data but we absolutely
run regressions and which was a it's a
interesting process that we've gone
through yeah and so we're talk about llm
as a judge which is the the llm looks at
the answer and says the result I see in
the golden set seems sufficiently
familiar sufficiently similar to the
result of product the live product gave
right now and then you I found
interesting in the blog post that you
you wrote about this there's this notion
of llm jury which I has has the risk
taking the analogy a bit too far but I
guess is that do you want to say a
couple words about that uh it's exactly
what it sounds like just multiple you
want to assess not just one voice but
multiple voices to make sure that you're
aligning and I guess partly a means to
deal with the fact that llms themselves
like the evaluator itself is a random or
is a non-deterministic entity so oddly
actually quite aligned to the reason
there is a judge and jury in the actual
human judicial system that's a yeah
that's a good point yeah because people
are nondeterministic too yeah yeah it's
like it's built in our image
in versus maybe non-enterprise or
consumer version of it but are there
other highlights I think the things I
captured so far have been the fact that
you have to use their model you can
necessarily see their data maybe even
the fundamental architecture of being
rag based because you're going to be
dealing with sensitive data I guess what
other
things jump to mind in terms of the
difference between building a chpt for
everybody and a chpt for the
Enterprise uh the biggest one is the one
you cited for chat GPT for consumers
it's run off the internet where
everything is public knowledge so you'd
never have to worry about permissions
but the other thing is when you're
building search for Consumer versus
Enterprise the signals that you use for
ranking are different so in consumer
search you have a lot of Click signals
because you have millions ions maybe
billions of people using it so it's very
dense your click signals and you're like
semantic similarities your synonyms you
just have a lot more data to go on so
the kind of signals you get in the
Enterprise you're not going to get the
anchors that you have in search this the
density of Click they're very sparse
your click data in the Enterprise is too
sparse to use that but then you have
different data you have activity data
you have oh this document like a lot of
people are us looking at this document
in the last week so it must be important
to Let's bump it up you have the what I
talked about of knowing your team if I'm
looking for an onboarding document for
my team I'm not going to use one from
marketing I'm going to use one from
somebody else in engineering or somebody
in my team to as a template to start
from so we that's a signal that that has
no meaning in consumer but is very
important in the Enterprise things like
activity and proximity like how
proximity of the person looking at right
the document what is her proximity to me
so we personalization is a very strong
signal in glean for doing ranking which
it's a much weaker signal in consumer so
that is what the team spent the first
couple years figuring out is what are
the Enterprise signals that you need for
ranking yeah and the first the whole
architecture predicates on the fact that
the first problem is find the relevant
pieces of information in the Enterprise
and then subsequently as we've discussed
before the Gen ux on top of them is how
you interact with that data versus
pointing elsewhere which opens up its
own set of opportunities and and at the
same time maybe challenges around
adoption because it's in new practice
and I guess the what is your sense
around Enterprises Readiness to embrace
all this new stuff on it are they
chomping at the bit to to take it are
they trying to stay away and just do the
minimal whatever board requirements to
the AI they're more ready than I thought
like cios are like we need an AI
solution and they're all going out there
and evaluating different AI Solutions
now part of it is a checkbox because the
board is telling them they need an AI
solution but there's a lot who are
genuinely interested and genuinely
curious I mean you see a lot of it
departments and large companies building
using open AI to try and build their own
Solutions a lot of come to us a year
later and we tried to build this it's
hard didn't realize how hard rag is we
should use your API guys but that so I
do think that there is a willingness
there's also some fear so some companies
are like I even if you say you're secure
I just don't want any AI coming anywhere
near me and those we don't even talk to
but I have been encouraged by how many
want to bring it in and then after they
bring it in you have the Champions who
really are like vocal and figure out how
to use it that's what's going to take
the biggest the a biggest change
management is how do you under how do
you uh really educate everyone on how
much they can make their jobs better how
much they can leverage products like
glean to be more productive because as I
said with the chat GPT example people
just forget sometimes and just don't
even think of it yeah and humans change
the
slowest so that's a good teup to the
final question here we talked about the
zero to one how do people even wrap
their heads around what is it they could
do what do you imagine as the far down
the road reality I talk about AI native
software development talk about AI
native and a bunch of things what is the
AI native reality I don't if that's the
right term here for Enterprise surge for
Glen's Vision I think that people are
going to be able to automate away a lot
of what they do today a lot of the toil
that they do today and if you think of
people some people Executives has have
assistance you'll have essentially an
assistant for every aspect of what you
do and you're not going to have to do a
lot of this like writing the first
versions of your documents prepping for
your customers uh we had a a finance
person build a glean impr prompt to help
her figure out comp for salespeople read
the spreadsheet and understand which
salesperson is getting what comp based
on what they've done like all these
things people are doing manually and
people will just get used to it'll be a
new thing they won't even they'll even
forget when they used to have to do it
manually and that'll be okay because
they don't need that skill anymore and
they can spend time on other things
other hopefully more creative higher
leverage things I'm looking forward to
that day yeah and it is it safe it
sounds compelling for sure and I guess
you and I have both been in sort of
leadership positions and so sometimes
spoiled with having some of that work
happen with with others on the team do
you find that to be a good mental model
is it like everybody would be a bit more
senior in their org with having a whole
whole bunch of helpers around them and
the type of
work the average person or whatever even
the more sort of lower down the
hierarchy of an organization would be
doing would end up being more senior
compared to what we're doing today more
managerial I I've heard somebody
describe it as it's like having teams of
interns and so I don't I wouldn't put it
as everyone will be more managerially I
don't believe that but I believe if you
had interns who could do a lot of the
wrote automated work that can easily be
automated so you can do the Creative
work and so I think you will get more
productivity if if you all if everybody
had this five or six interns to go build
this code here build that document there
that presentation I think we'd all be I
I think happier in in how we're spending
our time yep yep like I absolutely agree
with that tomorrow this has been
excellent I'm sure we could go on for a
full extra hour to dig into it but
thanks a lot for coming on the show and
sharing a whole bunch of these
learnings thank you for having me it's
always great to talk to you and thanks
everybody for tuning in and I hope you
join us for the next
[Music]
[Applause]
one thanks for tuning in join us next
time on the AI native Dev brought to you
by Tesla
[Music]